Guide to the
Brown University Library
- IRS Payment Letter Sep 2013.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2013-08-29 16:52:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-10 00:20:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW chapter 8 sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 8 Do Your Gender Mindfully/Date created: 2012-06-30 05:07:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 05:38:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- A Queer and Pleasant Mistress.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Date created: 2011-09-08 11:39:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-08 12:13:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 4 Sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 4 Let Why = Why/Date created: 2012-06-30 02:08:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 02:09:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- QueerPleasantBookCoverTextPush.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Layout & Design/QueerPleasantCover ƒ/Date created: 2011-05-27 16:21:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-27 18:37:08 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Now With Beacon/Date created: 2011-08-23 10:33:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-23 10:33:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KATE BORNSTEIN TOUR.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/8D5A1E6A-3871-48CC-B85B-B014FE3DEA28/Tour Venues Booked.mbox/Been There, Done That.mbox/UK Tour Feb 2016.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/2/8/2/Attachments/282661/1/Date created: 2016-01-03 16:38:34 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-03 16:38:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Brown Anthology Piece Text Bits.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-04-27 15:05:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-04-27 15:05:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- New What is Tantra Chapter KBpass1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/8/5/3/Attachments/358707/1/Date created: 2017-02-26 11:11:19 EST-0500Date modified: 2017-02-26 11:11:19 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- pages compatibility check kb pass 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Technical Problems SOLVED/Date created: 2011-07-29 10:08:38 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-29 10:08:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- cheap sex with bc 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/BC this and that/Date created: 2009-02-02 18:12:57 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-02 18:41:14 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Family Man.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/ Book 2, Chapter 4/New York, the First Time ƒ/Date created: 2009-01-17 11:44:57 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-06 15:07:24 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- TORI LOR to JCHP.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2010-02-07 13:42:17 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-08 15:17:10 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 6 MNGW chapter 6 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 6 SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX/Date created: 2012-07-15 11:08:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 11:09:23 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Masque for John #1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/JohnEmigh Masque NYC/Date created: 2009-02-09 15:48:45 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-03-03 15:35:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 2 2.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Attic/Book Two IP/Date created: 2011-08-07 15:34:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-19 02:06:01 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dixie Belle June 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Letters to Tom/Date created: 2011-06-27 22:22:00 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-27 22:22:21 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Acknowledgments Plain.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Acknowledgements ƒ/Date created: 2012-07-14 14:33:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 15:36:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Queer and Pleasant Danger Part 3 Gold.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Cleanest, Newest/Date created: 2011-08-31 13:37:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-31 13:43:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- GO TNG Blog.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Hello Cruel Blog/Date created: 2009-07-11 12:29:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-07-12 17:46:35 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Performance Version Crossed Genres.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Crossed Genres/Date created: 2010-09-07 11:57:19 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-07 12:01:17 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 1 MNGW Chapter 1 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-07-14 14:28:46 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-14 14:30:35 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- raw thank you tweets.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Tweet Folder/Date created: 2012-07-07 18:35:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-07 18:35:25 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 10/Date created: 2012-05-14 13:28:34 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-14 15:50:07 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Sassafrass Submission 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-01-14 11:26:21 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-14 11:26:21 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- avb_obit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Alan Eulogy/Date created: 2008-12-30 15:24:32 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-11 17:10:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Book 2 Chapter 5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 2 Chap 5/Date created: 2009-11-29 17:36:12 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-09 11:53:35 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2012 Talk to CCSU 3rd Annual Lavender Commencement.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2012-05-03 11:50:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-03 18:03:16 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 3 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 3 Let X = X/Date created: 2012-06-29 23:40:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-01 20:47:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Qs to author December 7.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Copy Edits/Date created: 2013-01-02 12:19:55 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-02 12:19:55 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Theater, and Future of the Body.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/art pieces/Date created: 2010-10-04 01:28:38 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-04 01:28:38 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- final proposal.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/NYS college health assoc conf/Date created: 2011-08-17 09:19:39 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-17 09:19:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Collections Letter June 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Date created: 2011-06-21 09:44:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-21 10:24:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Blurb Letter Patti Smith.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2011-09-27 17:55:26 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-28 13:27:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Author Questionnaire Kate Bornstein.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Publicity/Date created: 2011-04-23 21:21:34 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-24 16:20:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2 MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass (Kate Bornstein's conflicted copy 2012-10-21).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-05-23 16:15:59 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-10-16 22:25:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- JVB Interview.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/JustinVBond/Date created: 2011-09-07 19:05:55 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-07 19:05:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- dvd label 4 lana kar.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Futa for Lana and Kar/Date created: 2009-09-03 14:04:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-03 19:00:38 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- charts for role play.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Workshop Handouts/Role Play Workshop/Date created: 2009-03-18 11:57:07 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-18 12:26:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 8 MNGW chapter 8 Gold sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 8 Do Your Gender Mindfully/Date created: 2012-07-15 11:49:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 11:50:35 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Team Spirit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 19:13:19 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 19:15:31 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 09-106 LGBTA 2-11 Speaker.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/Stony Brook 09/Date created: 2009-02-09 14:17:27 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-09 18:50:10 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Not Guilty Plea—Bus Ticket.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2011-08-03 11:38:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-03 11:48:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- My Virginity.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Readings for Dixon Place/Date created: 2012-04-29 17:49:30 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-29 23:14:00 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate Bornstein full clean edit.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/It Gets Better Book/Date created: 2010-12-22 18:41:30 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-12-22 18:49:47 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/7/1/Attachments/177402/2/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:53:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:53:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Repair Return Note Etymotic.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Receipts/Date created: 2009-02-13 10:09:51 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-13 10:59:10 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- University of Florida 102212 itinerary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/University Central Florida 2012/Date created: 2012-10-21 15:47:23 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-10-21 15:47:23 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-1 Beta 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 3 Chapter 1/Date created: 2010-06-23 16:54:49 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-06-23 18:32:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 6 SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX/Date created: 2012-05-28 13:03:23 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-29 15:53:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- novotesforbulliescontract.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Date created: 2011-09-27 17:03:22 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-27 17:03:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- CBST Pride Shabat Talk.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2012-06-21 16:47:22 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-22 14:04:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-06-09 15:33:41 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-06-09 15:52:53 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 1 MNGW Chapter 1_KBpass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-05-15 11:51:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-14 14:26:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/7/1/Attachments/177505/2/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- contract U Miss.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/U Miss/Date created: 2009-02-23 21:30:27 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-23 21:30:27 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 0 MNGW TOC & Intro.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-07-08 14:30:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 15:34:26 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Transgender Day Remembrance 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2009-11-19 12:10:46 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-20 01:35:36 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Post registration form London 2015.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/2/6/2/Attachments/262977/2.2/Date created: 2015-10-07 12:47:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-07 12:47:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Lucia Miel 1st draft.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-02-07 13:32:12 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-07 15:17:04 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Play List for @largeheartedboy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Large Hearted Boy Playlist/Date created: 2012-05-25 14:49:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-25 15:21:32 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better KB 2nd pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/BC Ecstasy Is Neccessary/Date created: 2012-02-29 11:19:28 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-29 11:23:03 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 0-Introduction.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2010-07-09 10:30:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-09 10:30:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB-Career-Summary-2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Bios-KB/Date created: 2010-07-09 12:27:34 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-09 13:01:06 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 5 KB Edit Chap 5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-15 23:20:11 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-16 21:33:16 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Crystal Letter page two.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Crystal Yakacki/Date created: 2010-10-12 12:30:42 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-11-12 10:10:47 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- TWEETS ETC.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/57F6CF73-8A8B-4A58-8154-FFD84FE00244/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/9/1/Attachments/190235/2/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:09 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 11 KB Edit Gnite Gday and Acks.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-19 13:28:37 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-19 14:55:53 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- B's pass_TOTWK_by_KB_for_OutMag.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/TOd Trannies W Knives/Date created: 2010-04-15 15:47:11 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-15 16:18:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dear Galley Reader Letter.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/2/8/1/Attachments/182056/1/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:21 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Femme Conf 2010 Keynote No Restrictions.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Femme Conf Keynote/Date created: 2010-08-13 12:49:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-13 14:27:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW rainbow anarchy trans ruby slippers.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-24 16:34:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-24 16:56:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 13-14 newsletter.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Newsletters/2013-2014 Catalogue/Date created: 2013-01-29 11:47:49 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-30 17:53:06 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- derby gender essay draft 5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-01-24 15:53:11 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-24 15:53:11 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Medical Records Request.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Block Center/Date created: 2013-02-27 16:34:27 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-02-27 16:34:27 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2006-2009 Ltrs to IRS-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Taxes/KB 2009 Taxes/Date created: 2010-08-31 13:41:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-31 14:52:38 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Queer and Pleasant Book 3, 2.1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-23 21:30:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-29 17:55:54 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages